[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why was the passion fruit given this interesting name?", "correct_answer": "It has a religious connotation.", "incorrect_answers": ["Because of its sweet smell.", "Because it was considered an aphrodisiac.", "Because it tastes very sweet."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Platypuses use this method to detect their prey.", "correct_answer": "They use electrolocation.", "incorrect_answers": ["They rely on their well-developed sense of smell.", "Platypuses rely mainly on their hearing.", "They rely on their exceptional eyesight."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these songs, inducted into the Grammy Hall of Fame, was not recorded by the singer-songwriter, born Robert Allen Zimmerman?", "correct_answer": "Aint No Mountain High Enough", "incorrect_answers": ["Mr. Tambourine Man", "Like a Rolling Stone", "Blowin in the Wind"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Termites are not actually ants.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which list is in increasing order regarding size?", "correct_answer": "Squad, Platoon, Company, Brigade", "incorrect_answers": ["Squad, Platoon, Battalion, Company", "Platoon, Company, Regiment , Battalion", "Platoon, Squad, Company, Regiment"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This film-within-a-film, written and directed by Woody Allen, tells the story of a film character who leaves the black-and-white film and enters the colorful real world.", "correct_answer": "The Purple Rose of Cairo", "incorrect_answers": ["Love and Death", "Crimes and Misdemeanors", "Stardust Memories"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In chess, the king should be used aggressively in the endgame.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This small agricultural town, whose motto is solidarity in work, is located in Quebec, Canada, near the St. Lawrence River.", "correct_answer": "Saint-Louis-du-Ha!-Ha!", "incorrect_answers": ["Cape Circumcision", "Broken Back Springs", "Readymoney Cove"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1864, the US government issued a two-cent coin. What was so special about this coin ?", "correct_answer": "It was the first to say In God We Trust", "incorrect_answers": ["It was golden", "It was shunned by the South", "It was the first to have a picture of a President on it"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 17th century a ban was placed on eating meat during lent but the beaver meat was not included in that ban.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these names refers to the Crab-eating Fox, a medium-sized fox found in the central part of South America?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Forest Fox", "Wood Fox", "Common Fox"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Researchers in England found this to be true of  blond cashiers in supermarkets.", "correct_answer": "Gather greater queues", "incorrect_answers": ["Have frequent technical issues with the registers", "Receive more tips from customers", "Have higher chances of not balancing the register at the end of the day"]}]